<resources>
    <string name="dokter_gigi">A dentist is a doctor who specializes in studying health and diseases of the teeth and mouth. A dentist has competence or expertise in diagnosing, treating, and providing education about the prevention of various dental, gum, and oral health problems.</string>
    <string name="dokter_umum">General practitioners are health professionals who will provide care and treatment. The scope of the cases they handle is more general. They will treat patients with general health problems. These health workers can also provide referrals to patients who need more intensive treatment to specialist doctors.</string>
    <string name="dokter_saraf">A neurologist or neurologist is a specialist who diagnoses and treats problems related to the brain and nervous system. Neurology is concerned with the diagnosis and treatment of all categories of conditions and diseases involving the central and peripheral nervous systems (somatic and automatic nervous systems).</string>
    <string name="dokter_mata">An ophthalmologist is a doctor who has specific expertise in providing examinations, treatments, and diagnoses related to eye diseases and visual disturbances. Not only that, ophthalmologists also have competence in handling eye surgery.</string>
    <string name="dokter_dalam">Internal medicine doctors are specialists who treat various complaints, symptoms, and health problems related to almost all organ systems in the bodies of adult and elderly patients. Internal medicine doctors have the expertise and competence to treat various diseases that cannot be handled by general practitioners.</string>
    <string name="dokter_gizi">Nutritionists are specialists in charge of providing advice and information to patients on the management of nutrition and health problems, involved in the diagnosis and treatment of health problems related to nutrition and nutrition.</string>
    <string name="dokter_jantung">Cardiologists are doctors who specialize in diseases of the heart and the circulatory system (cardiovascular). Cardiologists are trained in diagnosing, treating, and preventing a variety of conditions associated with heart disease, such as high blood pressure, heart rhythm disorders, to potentially life-threatening strokes.</string>
    <string name="article_covid">JAKARTA, KOMPAS.com - Positive confirmation cases of Covid-19 in the country continue to increase every day. On Thursday (1/7/2021), active Covid-19 cases reached 253,826 cases. This number is the highest during the Covid-19 pandemic in Indonesia. This figure is equivalent to 11.5 percent of the total confirmed cases of Covid-19. Meanwhile, yesterday, Wednesday (30/6/2021), the number of active patients was 239,368. The active cases are patients who have tested positive for Covid-19 and are undergoing treatment. This figure is obtained by reducing the total number of positive cases of Covid-19 with the number of cures and deaths.</string>
    <string name="article_health">Jakarta, CNN Indonesia -- Finance Minister Sri Mulyani increased the health budget in the ceiling for handling COVID-19 and National Economic Recovery (PEN) by Rp. 13.14 trillion from Rp. 172.84 trillion to Rp. 185.98 trillion. health services for covid-19 vaccination, treatment (therapeutic), and covid-19 care. Jakarta, CNN Indonesia -- Finance Minister Sri Mulyani increased the health budget in the ceiling for handling COVID-19 and National Economic Recovery (PEN) by Rp. 13.14 trillion from Rp. 172.84 trillion to Rp. 185.98 trillion. health services for covid-19 vaccination, treatment (therapeutic), and covid-19 care.</string>
    <string name="rhanks">Thank you FSD Drugstore application customers for queuing online and have a nice day. Hopefully this application can help customers queue to reduce the spread in the pandemic era.</string>
    <string name="article_food">Jakarta - Consumption of healthy food before and after the vaccine is important to maintain body fitness. Here are five recommended diets before and after the Covid-19 vaccine.
The Covid-19 vaccine is being intensively carried out to create herd immunity which is expected by the government. But the vaccine does not mean it will make the body will not get the coronavirus.
Even after the vaccine, maintaining health and following the established health protocols must continue to be carried out so that the body is farthest from the virus. A healthy lifestyle also greatly determines the effect of the vaccine received and the symptoms that arise after getting the vaccine.</string>
    <string name="app_home">The FSD Drugstore application is an application developed by the CDD Team of POLIWANGI students with the aim of creating a useful mobile application when queuing drugs at the pharmacy. Using the mobile application is quite easy where users just turn on the internet and choose a queue number to order prescription drugs from the doctor.</string>
</resources>